<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Git on</title><link>http://joekratzat.com/tags/git/</link><description>Recent content in Git on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Joe Kratzat</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 21:14:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://joekratzat.com/tags/git/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploying Hugo site using wercker to github</title><link>http://joekratzat.com/post/2016/deploying-hugo-site-using-wercker-to-github/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 21:14:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://joekratzat.com/post/2016/deploying-hugo-site-using-wercker-to-github/</guid><description>After moving to Hugo from Jekyll I needed to setup auto-deploy changes to my github page. Originally it was set up to use a deploy.sh script from the Hugo blog post. That just isn&amp;rsquo;t good enough. I&amp;rsquo;m lazy and I want the computer to do the work for me.
Wercker Hugo has another great post, automated deployments using wercker. Since I split up my source and site repos from the previous Hugo post for my personal page I had to make one tweak to the wercker.</description></item><item><title>jenkins and bitbucket</title><link>http://joekratzat.com/post/2013/jenkins-and-bitbucket/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 22:11:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://joekratzat.com/post/2013/jenkins-and-bitbucket/</guid><description>Tonight I had to setup a new instance of Jenkins. Having never set Jenkins to work with Bitbucket before I thought this might help out others. This will cover Jenkins accessing only Bitbucket, having it deploy might be another post, but that isn&amp;rsquo;t covered here.
Jenkins install Starting out, I have a blank Digital Ocean droplet. There is basically nothing. I had to install Jenkins, which is pretty basic:</description></item><item><title>Git: a powerful front-end to Subversion</title><link>http://joekratzat.com/post/2012/git-a-powerful-front-end-to-subversion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 22:13:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://joekratzat.com/post/2012/git-a-powerful-front-end-to-subversion/</guid><description>Git is a great version control system. I have used it for some time on many different projects and I really enjoy working with it. My life is bit simpler because of Git.
When I had to move back to SVN I didn&amp;rsquo;t really like the idea of losing local features branches, stashing , and easy merging. Luckily, Git has the a svn command which allows me to use Git as my front end to SVN.</description></item></channel></rss>